Guide to the Medical Center records, 1825-2005 RG0007
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Medical staff office files, 1969-1989; RG0007 Series 2; 12 Linear feet
  - Proposed by-laws and procedures, 07/1975-06/1976 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Proposed by-laws and procedures: ACD Procedures, 07/1975-06/1977 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Proposed by-laws and procedures, 07/1977-06/1981 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Proposed by-laws committee: List of members, minutes, and correspondence, 07/1975-06/1976 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Proposed by-laws committee: Reports, of the clinic, and constitution, 07/1975-06/1976 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Proposed by-laws committee: Minutes, undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
    Before 1975
  - Proposed by-laws committee: Reports, constitution, and by-laws drafts, 07/1976-06/1977 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Proposed by-laws committee: List of members, minutes, and correspondence, 07/1976-06/1977 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Proposed by-laws committee: Minutes and correspondence, 07/1977-06/1978 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Budget and Finance committee: Members, minutes, and procedures, 07/1976-06/1977 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Budget and Finance committee: Correspondence and special reports, 07/1976-06/1977 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Budget and Finance committee: Members and minutes, 07/1977-06/1978 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Audit committee: Correspondence, 07/1984-06/1985 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Audit committee: Committee list, 07/1985-06/1986 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Audit committee, 1984-1986 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    Dates include 10/10/1984; 11/18/1985; 05/05/1986; and 06/10/1986
  - Audit committee, 06/1986-11/1986 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Audit committee, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    Dates include January 30; March 20; and June 30
  - Capital equipment: Minutes, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Capital equipment: Emergency requests, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Capital equipment: Dermatology, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Capital equipment: Medicine, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Capital equipment: Neurosurgery, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Capital equipment: Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Capital equipment: Opthamology, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Capital equipment: Psychiatry, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Capital equipment: Radiology, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Capital equipment: Surgery, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Capital equipment: Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Capital equipment: Minutes, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Capital equipment: Dermatology, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Capital equipment: Opthamology, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Capital equipment: Psychiatry, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Capital equipment: Medicine, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Capital equipment: Radiology, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Capital equipment: Urology, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Capital equipment: Surgery, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Capital equipment: Neurosurgery, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Capital equipment: Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Capital equipment: Budget, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Capital equipment: Approved lists, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Capital equipment: Emergency requests, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Capital equipment: Minutes, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Capital equipment: Memoranda, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Capital equipment: Ambulatory physical therapy, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Capital equipment: Dermatory, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Capital equipment: Medicine, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Capital equipment: Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Capital equipment: Opthamology, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Capital equipment: Psychiatry, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Capital equipment: Radiology, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Capital equipment: Surgery, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Capital equipment: Urology, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Capital equipment: Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Advisory Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Advisory Committee: List of members and minutes, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Advisory Committee: Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Advisory Committee: Reports, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Advisory Committee: List of members and minutes, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Advisory Committee: Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Advisory Committee: Space requests, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Advisory Committee: Capital expenditure requests, 07/1976-06/1977 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Advisory Committee: List members and minutes, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Advisory Committee: Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Advisory Committee: Ad hoc lab procedures, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Advisory Committee: Minutes, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Advisory Committee: Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Advisory Committee: Medical director search, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Advisory Committee: Minutes, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Advisory Committee: Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Advisory Committee: Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Advisory Committee: List of members and minutes, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Advisory Committee: Agendas, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Advisory Committee: Bad debt subcommittee, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Advisory Committee: Ad hoc lab procedures, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Advisory Committee: Reports, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Advisory Committee: Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Advisory Committee: Minutes and members, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Advisory Committee: Space requirements, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Advisory Committee: Agendas, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Advisory Committee: Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Advisory Committee: Minutes, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Advisory Committee: Agendas, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Advisory Committee: Subcommittee, 07/1982 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Advisory Committee: List of members and minutes, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Advisory Committee: Agenda, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Advisory Committee: Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Administrative contacts: Minutes and correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Administrative contacts: Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Administrative contacts: Meetings, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Medical Faculty Associates: Administrative contacts, 07/1981-06/1982 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Medical Faculty Associates: Administrative contacts, 07/1982-06/1983 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Medical Faculty Associates: Administrative contacts, 07/1983-06/1984 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Medical Faculty Associates: Administrative contacts meeting, 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Medical Faculty Associates: ACWG, 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Medical Faculty Associates: Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Medical Faculty Associates: Administrative contacts, 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Executive Committee: Clinic by-laws, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Clinic procedures, attendance, agendas, list of members, and minutes, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Executive Committee: Dates, minutes, correspondence, and statistics, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Executive Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    Includes procedures of the ambulatory care division, list of committee members, attendance, dates, agendas, minutes, and statistics
  - Executive Committee: Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Executive Committee: Special reports, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Executive Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    Includes list of members, attendance, dates, agendas, minutes, and subcommittee minutes
  - Executive Committee: Statistics and correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Executive Committee: Special reports and announcements, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Executive Committee: Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Executive Committee: Agendas, list of members, and minutes, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Personnel files, circa 1970-circa 1989; RG0007 Series 3; 10.5 Linear feet
  This series consists of personnel files of inactive medical staff. The dates of the materials is not readily attainable, but generally fall in the range of the 1970's-80's.
  - Albaster, Oliver, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Avery, Gordon, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Allman, Robert, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Ballard, Roberta, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Batipps, Michael, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Barnett, Marjorie, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Barr, Solomon, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Bartman, Barbara, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Baxter, Daniel, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Bayer, Laurie, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Bean, Barbara, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Becker, Matthew, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Berler, David, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Bhan, Anjana, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Black, Edward, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Bouchlas, Constantine, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Bokhart, Farhat, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Bowles, Lawrence, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Boyd, Allen, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Bray, Anne, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Britton, John, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Cantwell, Kathleen, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Carabell, Steven, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Carroll, Barbara, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Casey, David, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Castle, Robert, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Chacko, Leela, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Chan, Clara, undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Chang, Frank, undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Chavis, Richard, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Chin-Lee, William, undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Cholmondeley, Tessa, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Christov-Bakargiev, D., undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Clawson, Gary, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Cockerham, John, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Cohen, George, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Coultrip, Laura, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Curtis, David, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Daee, Said, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Davis, James, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Day, Robert, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Derusso, Franklin, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Dosovitz, Ira, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Ehrlich, Bernard, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Elon, Rebecca, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Evans, James, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Fakhry, Samir, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Feaster, Samuel, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Fenton, Barbara, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Fernicola, Marie, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Filart, Roland, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Fine, Ronald, undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Fischer, Max, undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Fishman, Ronald, undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Francis, Carolyn, undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Friedman, A. Jerry, undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Arnold, Friedman, undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Galioto, Frank, undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Garcia, Jorge, undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Garrett, Margaret, undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Garro, Juan, undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Glew, William, undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Golding, Martin, undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Greenfield, Alfred, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Griffin, Suzanne, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Grillion, George, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Grossman, Richard, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Guzzetta, Philip, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Hall, William, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Hanson, Peggy, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Heath, Diane, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Henriques, Horace, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Herr, Daniel, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Herz, Elisabeth, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Hershkowitz, Melvin, undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Herzog, William, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Higginbotham, Edith, undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Hillenbrand, Elizabeth, undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Hoffman, Julius, undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Hsu, Irene, undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Hudkins, Catherine, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Hustead, Arthur, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Jagoda, Andy, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Jani, Niranjan, undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Jannota, Frank, undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Jason, Casey, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Jeney, Richard, undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Jones, Eleanor, undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Joseph, Krishna, undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Kantrowitz, Micki, undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Katz, Linda, undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Kavit, Gary, undated (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Kaufman, Charles, undated (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Kaur, Shubjeet, undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Kefale, Georgis, undated (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Kevess-Cohen, Ruth, undated (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Kloman, Alexander, undated (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Kotlyarov, Eduardo, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Kuehl, Karen, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Kushner, Edward, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Kwon, Nancy, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Landy, Helain, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Lear, Arnold, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Leavitt, Jacqueline, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Leikin, Sanford, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Letterman, Gordon, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Levi, David, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Levitt, Robert, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Levy, Michael, undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Levy, Warren, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Lewit, Robert, undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Linden, Craig, undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Littman, Burt, undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Lloyd, Bruce, undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Lynn, Hoanne, undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Mcafee, John, undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Mcconnaughy, Richard, undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Manfredi, Rita, undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - March, Mollyann, undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Mau, Marjorie, undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Mekky, Siza, undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Mercado, Flavia, undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Mills, Mitchell, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Mizus, Irving, undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Morales, George, undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Mekherjee, Ashis, undated (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Rosen, Leonard, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Rubovits-Seitz, Philip, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Sager, Alan, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Santangelo, Cesare, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Scavo, Louis, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Scheidemandel, Heinz, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Schneider, Helen, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Schneiderman, Charles, undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Schulof, Richard, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Schultz, Richard, undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Schumann, Harry, undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Schurter, Maxine, undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Shah, Jayesh, undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Shapiro, Stephen, undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Sheffery, Joseph, undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Siegel, Karen, undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Silver, Harold, undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Singer, Alan, undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Singer, Janet, undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Skudder, Paul, undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Slimak, Randall, undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Snyder, Christopher, undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Sokol, Gerald, undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Stein, Chester, undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Stone, Ann, undated (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Swope, John, undated (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Taylor, Scott, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Teich, Douglas, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Teno, Joan, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Thiet, Mari-Paule, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Thompson, Charles, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Titus, Elijah, undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Trotsky, Martin, undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Turner, Elsie, undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Vanderwalde, Joseph, undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Walsh, James, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Wechsler, Herbert, undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Witte, Jeffrey, undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Wurm, Scott, undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Yates, Harold, undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Yessler, Paul, undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Zamick, Paul, undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Zuckerman, Jonathan, undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Albala, David, undated (Box 7, Folder 18.1)
  - Buck, David, undated (Box 7, Folder 18.2)
  - Cooper, Betsy, undated (Box 7, Folder 18.3)
  - Deveikas, John, undated (Box 7, Folder 18.4)
  - Dolmatch, Bart, undated (Box 7, Folder 18.5)
  - Glover, William, undated (Box 7, Folder 18.6)
  - Gulya, Aina, undated (Box 7, Folder 18.7)
  - Karle, Virginia, undated (Box 7, Folder 18.8)
  - Jones, Catherine, undated (Box 7, Folder 18.9)
  - Maxwell, Daniel, undated (Box 7, Folder 18.1)
  - Moore, W. Tabb, undated (Box 7, Folder 18.11)
  - Muldoon, Sheila, undated (Box 7, Folder 18.12)
  - Newman, Kurt, undated (Box 7, Folder 18.13)
  - Price, Susan, undated (Box 7, Folder 18.14)
  - Rakusan, Tamara, undated (Box 7, Folder 18.15)
  - Ripp, Nancy, undated (Box 7, Folder 18.16)
  - Rosenfeld, Richard, undated (Box 7, Folder 18.17)
  - Sanders, Nancy, undated (Box 7, Folder 18.18)
  - Schamp, David, undated (Box 7, Folder 18.19)
  - Schoenfeld, Burton, undated (Box 7, Folder 18.2)
  - Shelburne, Samuel, undated (Box 7, Folder 18.21)
  - Suatengco, Domingo, undated (Box 7, Folder 18.22)
  - Thompson, Virginia, undated (Box 7, Folder 18.23)
  - Van Breda, Arina, undated (Box 7, Folder 18.24)
- Articles and studies, 1932-1962; RG0007 Series 4; 1.5 Linear feet
  This series consists of writings (reprints) and studies from the medical school, and range in date from 1932-62.
  - Studies From The School of Medicine, George Washington University, 1932-1935 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Studies From The School of Medicine, George Washington University, 1935-1936 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Studies From The School of Medicine, George Washington University, 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Studies From The School of Medicine, George Washington University, 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Studies From The School of Medicine, George Washington University, 1938-1939 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Studies From The School of Medicine, George Washington University, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Studies From The School of Medicine, George Washington University, 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Studies From The School of Medicine, George Washington University, 1942-1943 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Collected Reprints, GWU School of Medicine, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    3 volumes
  - Postgraduate Education magazine with a section on GW and various medical studies, 04/1956 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Reprints, 1893-1918; RG0007 Series 5; 0.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series consists of 23 collected reprints of articles written by William Cline Borden (with biographical sketch), GW Medical School class of 1883. They range in date from 1893-1918.
  - The Origin and Development of the Fat Cell of the Frog, 1889 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    From The Microscope.
  - Stereoscopic Photomicrography, 1893 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    From The America Monthly Microscopic Journal.
  - The Fat Cell: Its Origin, Development, and Histological Position, 1894 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    From New York Medical Journal
  - The Vital Statistics of an Apache Indian Community, 1893 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    From Boston Medical and Surgical Journal.
  - Journal of the Royal Microscopical Society, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Development of Photomicrographic Negatives, 1896 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Slowly Absorbable Antiseptic Catgut by a Modification of the Boeckmann Method, 1897 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    From the Proceedings of the Seventh Annual Meeting of the Association of Military Surgeons of the United States.
  - Instruction in First Aid: Its Necessity in Modern Armies, 1899 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    From The Military Surgeon.
  - Gunshot Wounds: A Report of Gunshot Cases in the Spanish-American War, and Deductions There, 1900 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Traumatic Stricture of the Oesophagus: Operation by Abbey's Method, 1902 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    From Washington Medical Journals.
  - A Brief Showing the Work Done at the Army General Hospital, Washington, D.C., and the Necessity for Placing the Institution Upon a More Satisfactory Basis, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Relation of the Medical Department of the United States Army to the Profession, 1904 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    From Medicine.
  - An Essay On Military Surgery, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    From Government Printing Office.
  - The Proposed Medical Reserve Corps for the Army vs. Major Azel Ames' Opinions, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    From Journal of the Association of Military Surgeons of the United States.
  - The Walter Reed U.S. Army General Hospital, District of Columbia, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    From Washington Medical Annals.
  - The Trend of Medical Education in the United States, 1910 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    From New York Medical Journal.
  - Diagnosis, 1911 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Phi Chi Quarterly.
  - A History of Surgical Hemostasis, 1912 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Pericolic Adhesions, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    From Virginia Medical Semi-Monthly.
  - Suggestions for Correlating the Medical Schools of the Country with the Military, Naval, and Public Health Services of the United States, 1917 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    From Military Surgeon.
  - Greek and Roman Surgery, 1917 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Pasteur's Relation to Medicine and Surgery, 1918 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Treatment of Infected Wounds, 1918 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Chartering ceremony, 1997; RG0007 Series 6; 0.25 Linear feet (Box SHARED Box 6)
  This series consists of chartering ceremony documents of the school of public health and health services, and date from 1997. Formerly ACC#647
- Photographs and negatives, 1943-1987; RG0007 Series 7; 1 Linear foot (Box 1, Box 2)
  This series consists of prints and negatives used for the 1997 alumni reunion. They range in date from 1943-87 and include subjects such as Dr. Brian Blades in surgery, Dr. Tidball, President Marvin, classroom scenes, Dean Robert Keimowitz, follies, commencements, Dean Parks with Trustee E.K. Morris, J.Edgar Hoover.
  - Commencement and President's Tea, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Includes photograph
  - Commencement and President's Tea, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - John Liljenquist receives Upholm Award, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Dr. Brian Blades in surgery, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Negative only
  - Top Graduate Bob Liss takes awards, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Admiring 1967 Speculum (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Faculty, 05/04/1954 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Students in Biochemistry Lab, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Staff Meeting at Respiratory and Rehabilitation Center, 12/29/1959 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - GWU Medical Students at D.C. General Hospital, 03/1961 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Reserve Officers Training Corps, U.S. Army Medical Unit, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Univ. Pres. Thomas H. Carroll addresses Opening Assembly of GWU Med School, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Pres. Marvin, Dr. Parran, Dean Bloedorn, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - GW Medical Society dinner, 03/05/1949 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Class President presents award, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Edmund Ziman demonstrates heart device, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Dr. Tidball, 11/02/1964 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - School of Medicine, GWU, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Lab, School of Medicine, GWU, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Sesquicentennial events, 02/15/1971 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Commencement and President's Tea, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Classroom in the School of Medicine, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Gross Anatomy class, GW Med. School, circa 1980 (Box 1, Folder 23)